大家好，漂亮的人们都知道，人们转而使用Linux的最大原因之一就是使用
Hello you beautiful people know one of the biggest reasons for someone to switch to Linux is to use
可以说，Linux操作系统最强大的功能就是终端。
what is arguably the most powerful feature of the Linux operating system and that is the terminal.
如果你看过一部黑客或电脑天才坐在电脑后面打字的电影
Now if you've ever seen a film where a hacker or a computer genius has sat behind their computer typing
命令进入他们的计算机屏幕上看起来像是一个大黑盒的东西，这个黑盒被称为
commands into what looks like a big black box on their computer screen that black box is called the
终点站。
terminal.
现在，整个Linux操作系统一度完全是基于终端的。
Now at one time the entire Linux operating system was purely terminal based.
但是随着时间的推移，到目前为止已经开发出了更多的图形工具，我们有这些漂亮的
But as time has gone on more graphical tools have been developed up until now where we have these beautiful
桌面环境就像我们在Buntu上看到的那样。
desktop environments like what we see on a buntu.
现在从根本上讲，使用终端和使用普通图形方法之间的主要区别
Now fundamentally the main difference between using the terminal and using normal graphical methods
甚至在使用Windows或Mac时，您可能已经熟悉的一点是，它不是指向
that you're probably already familiar with from even using a Windows or a Mac is that instead of pointing
用鼠标点击来控制你的电脑，你就可以用键盘打字了。
and clicking with the mouse to control your computer you'll be typing with the keyboard instead.
现在Linux的独特之处在于，Linux的发展离不开终端。
Now Linux is unique in that the development of Linux is inseparable from the terminal.
这意味着知道如何使用终端可以让您在很大程度上控制如何使用终端
And this means that knowing how to use the terminal gives you pretty much absolute control over how
您的计算机通过使用终端工作。
your computer works by using the terminal.
您几乎可以在Linux计算机上做任何您想做的事情。
You can do pretty much anything that you want with your Linux computer.
现在，您无法在任何其他操作系统中对您的计算机进行这种级别的控制。
Now you can't get this level of control over your computer in any other operating system.
这使得终端成为一项令人难以置信的学习技能。
And this makes the terminal an incredible skill to learn.
现在，虽然它绝对很棒，但我知道航站楼一开始可能有点吓人
Now although it's absolutely awesome I understand that the terminal can be a bit intimidating at first
在这段视频中，我们将很容易地开始，我将向您展示如何实际
so in this video we're going to start off nice and easy and I'm going to show you how you can actually
在Buntu中打开和关闭终端。
open and close the terminal in a buntu.
在本视频结束时，您将在掌握Linux方面迈出非常重要的第一步
And by the end of this video you'll have taken a very important first step in your mastery of the Linux
操作系统，您还可以随意打开和关闭。
operating system and you'll also be able to open and close at will.
Linux提供的最强大的工具。
The most powerful tool that Linux has to offer.
那么让我们开始吧。
So let's go ahead and get started.
好的。
All right.
所以我们现在在一个漂亮的Buntu桌面上。
So here we are in a beautiful buntu desktop.
现在，我将向您展示如何继续使用图形方法打开终端。
Now I'm going to show you how you can go ahead and open the terminal using graphical methods.
现在沿着左下角，你会注意到一组九个点。
Now down the bottom left here you'll notice a a set of nine dots.
如果你把鼠标悬停在上面，上面写着“显示申请”。
And if you hover over it says show applications.
如果你点击它，它会以一种相当令人敬畏的方式打开。
If you click on that it will open up in a rather awesome way.
安装在您的计算机上的不同程序的完整列表，您可以四处查看
A whole list of different programs that are installed in your computer and you can just look around
在这里，你可以看到，好像你知道有一个日历，一个计算器，一些办公软件。
here you can see like you know there's a calendar a calculator some office software.
你可以继续向下滚动，那里有很多东西。
You can keep scrolling down and there's loads of things.
例如，Firefox Web浏览器、音乐播放器等等。
For example the Firefox web browser a music player and so on and so on.
就像你知道的，我鼓励你们看看这些东西，看看它们是怎么回事。
And like you know I encourage you to have a look at these and see what they do.
这就是您可以浏览计算机上的文件和诸如此类的内容的方式。
And this is how you can explore the files that are on your computer and things like that.
但是如果你向下滚动或者点击这里的第二个按钮，你会在这里看到一个叫做
But if you scroll down or you click this the second button over here you'll see a program here called
终点站。
terminal.
另一种方法是，您可以在搜索中进入顶部，只需键入Terminal，它就会
Another way to do it is you could just go at the top here in search and just type terminal and it will
直接上来吧。
come straight up.
现在，如果您继续点击它。
Now if you just go ahead and click on that.
我们到了。
Here we are.
您的终端窗口已打开。
Your terminal window has opened up.
在这里，我们将输入课程的命令，我们可以最大化终端。
So in here is where we're going to be typing the commands for the course we might maximize the terminal.
我们可以把它改小一点。
We might make it a bit smaller.
你可以在屏幕上移动，等等，顶部有很多不同的选项。
You can move it around the screen and so on and so on there's loads of different options at the top.
例如，您可以打开终端和可以编辑、复制和粘贴的内容。
For example you can open terminals and things you can edit copy and paste.
更改缩放和许多其他东西可以随心所欲地操作它，但它很容易打开
Change the zoom and so many other things play around with it as you wish but it's rather easy to open
如果您想要像在任何其他图形系统上一样关闭它。
if you want to close it just like you would on any other graphical system.
您只需单击顶部的X即可。
You just click the X at the top there.
好的。
OK.
这就是你打开和关闭航站楼的方式，这很容易做到，而且只有一次
So that's how you go ahead and open and close the terminal which is rather easy to do and it's Once
你已经做过一两次了，你可能不会忘记。
you've done it once or twice you probably won't forget it.
但是也有一些键盘快捷键可以让这个过程变得更快。
But there's also some keyboard shortcuts that will make this process a whole lot faster.
例如，如果只想使用键盘打开终端，可以按Ctrl、Alt和
For example if you want to open the terminal using just your keyboard you can press control alt and
字母T，您会发现所有终端都弹出了，如果您想要关闭它
the letter T and you will find that there were all the terminal pops up and if you want to close it
你只需按下Ctrl+D即可。
you just press control and D.
然后它就消失了。
And it goes away.
所以你可以看到，如果不控制T和Open的控件D，这会发生得有多快
So you can see how quickly this how quick this might happen you don't control T and Open's control D
然后它就会关闭。
and it shuts.
好的。
OK.
所以你就在这里。
So there you are.
这就是您可以使用图形方法和键盘快捷键打开和关闭终端的方式。
That's how you can open and close the terminal using both graphical methods and keyboard shortcuts.
您已经迈出了很好的第一步，应该开始感觉更像一个Linux专业人员了，因为
You've an excellent first step already and should start feeling a bit more like a Linux pro because
现在您知道如何实际打开和关闭航站楼了。
now you know how to actually open and close the terminal.
它就像您计算机上的任何其他程序一样。
It's just like any other program on your computer.
它并不可怕，实际上很容易使用，正如我们将在接下来的几个视频中向您展示的那样。
It's not scary and it's actually rather easy to use as we'll show you in the next few videos.
但这才是你的训练真正开始的地方，在下一个视频中，你将会跑你的第一个
But here's where your training really begins in the next video you're going to be running your first
终端中的命令。
commands in the terminal.
相信我，他们真的很棒。
And trust me they're pretty awesome.
所以，天哪，我会在下一个视频里见到你的。
So for not goodness I'll see you in the next video.